Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
["No One Mourns the Wicked"
playing]
[twinkling orchestral music]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
[sweeping music]
♪ ♪
- [vocalizing]
[music building]
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
- ♪ Good news ♪
♪ She's dead ♪
♪ The Witch of the West
is dead ♪
♪ The wickedest witch
there ever was ♪
♪ The enemy of all of us
here in Oz ♪
♪ Is dead ♪
♪ Good news ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Look!
It's Glinda!
- ♪ Let us be glad ♪
♪ Let us be grateful ♪
♪ Let us rejoicify
that goodness ♪
♪ Could subdue ♪
♪ The wicked workings of ♪
♪ You-know-who ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Isn't it nice to know ♪
♪ That good will
conquer evil? ♪
♪ The truth we all believe'll ♪
♪ By and by ♪
♪ Outlive a lie ♪
♪ For you and-- ♪
- It's good to see me,
isn't it?
[cheers and applause]
- Bowen.
What are you doing here?
- I, uh, paid
for the Bubble Machine
Meet and Greet Experience.
Is this not the line?
- No, this is--
this is the opening number.
- Then who did I Venmo?
OK, whatever.
Break legs, everyone.
Love you.
- Love you. See you later.
- See ya.
[cheers and applause]
- Now, where were we?
[dark music]
Thank you, former Broadway Biq.
♪ ♪
♪ No one mourns the Wicked ♪
♪ No one cries,
"They won't return" ♪
♪ No one lays a lily
on their grave ♪
♪ The good man
scorns the Wicked ♪
♪ Through their lives,
our children learn ♪
- ♪ What we miss
when we misbehave ♪
- ♪ And goodness knows ♪
♪ The wicked's lives
are lonely ♪
♪ Goodness knows ♪
♪ The wicked die alone ♪
♪ It just shows
when you're wicked ♪
♪ You're left only
on your own ♪
- ♪ Yes, goodness knows ♪
♪ The wicked's lives
are lonely ♪
♪ Goodness knows ♪
♪ The wicked cry alone ♪
♪ Nothing grows
for the wicked ♪
♪ They reap only ♪
♪ What they've sown ♪
♪ ♪
♪ No one mourns the Wicked ♪
♪ Now at last
she's dead and gone ♪
♪ Now at last there's joy
throughout the land ♪
♪ And goodness knows ♪
- ♪ Goodness knows ♪
- ♪ We know what goodness is ♪
♪ Goodness knows
the wicked die alone ♪
- ♪ She died alone ♪
- ♪ Woe to those,
woe to those ♪
♪ Who spurn what goodness is ♪
♪ They are shown ♪
♪ No one mourns the wicked ♪
- ♪ Good news ♪
- ♪ No one mourns the wicked ♪
- ♪ No one mourns ♪
♪ The wicked ♪
♪ Wicked ♪
[cheers and applause]
[mellow music]
- Fellow Ozians, hello.
[cheers and applause]
And please welcome
Cynthia Erivo
and our incredible
"Wicked" cast.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
- Ariana Grande, everybody.
[cheers and applause]
Welcome to "Wicked:
One Wonderful Night."
- And welcome, welcome, welcome
to the--
[cheers and applause]
To the legendary Dolby Theater
right here in Hollywood.
- The global impact
this movie has had
has been nothing short
of magical.
- Tonight, we will
celebrate the fans,
hear stories
from behind the scenes,
and even get a little tease
of what's still to come
in "Wicked: For Good."
[cheers and applause]
- You'll also see some
incredible musical performances
of all the songs from "Wicked"
that you know and love,
in ways
you've never seen before
and never will again.
- Being part of this cast
has been
one of the most life-changing
experiences for me.
Their talent and spirit
inspire me every day.
- "Wicked" is a movie
about friendship, love,
and defying every limit
placed upon you.
It's a story about honoring
those parts of ourselves
that don't fit the mold.
It's owning your difference
as a doorway to your power
and using that power to become
who you were always meant
to be.
This is "Wicked:
One Wonderful Night."
- Tonight, on "Wicked:
One Wonderful Night"...
- Everyone knows
that it's "Wicked."
No one and nothing is
bigger than this piece.
- A celebration of music,
wonder, and spectacle...
both: "Wicked"!
- With dazzling performances.
- Loving "Wicked"
isn't a hobby for me.
It is a lifestyle.
- The cast look back
on their "Wicked" experience.
- Most likely
to burst into song.
- ♪ Loathing ♪
♪ Loathing ♪
- And a once-in-a lifetime
performance
from the Gershwin Theatre,
featuring Stephen Schwartz
and two very special guests.
- You are truly wicked.
[applause]
- 305. Take one. Marker.
Did you keep any props
from set?
- I kept one of the books
from the library scene.
- I took Boq's handkerchief.
- There's a hat,
a pair of boots.
- One of the things I held onto
is this small piece of fabric
from the pajamas that I wore
in "What Is This Feeling?"
- Did I take anything to keep
as a kind of keepsake?
Well, um--hmm.
Yes, actually, I did.
Isn't that magnificent?
- He took the head?
- The giant one that I run
into in "The Wizard and I,"
he kept that?
- Isn't it, like, 10 feet tall?
- Does anyone know
what he does with that?
- [vocalizing]
As of late, I've been
taking it every place with me,
wherever I go.
[grunting]
Thank you.
I find it to be
very naturalistic and subtle.
It gives me great comfort.
- I think he likes it because
it's his head, you know.
And it's huge.
- No, no, no, it has
nothing to do with size.
I think these days
I can recognize
good craftsmanship and a kind
of mesmerizing artistry.
- Does it hang on a wall?
Does he just
carry it around with him?
- Ow.
- How does it move
around his home?
- Grab.
No, no, oh!
[crashes]
I like to think that this
statue kind of is me.
[softly singing]
♪ Together we're ♪
♪ Unlimited ♪
Hi, honey.
[claps]
Hey. Shh.
- Please welcome
Jeff Goldblum.
[cheers and applause]
- Thank you.
I love you.
Look at you.
Hi. Hi.
Thank you so much for coming.
My name is Jeff.
Hello. Hello.
Thank you.
Hey, who feels like a little
more singing and dancing?
You feel like that?
[cheers and applause]
Good.
Look what I see over here.
This is a piano.
Do you recognize it?
OK.
Let's see.
Oh, hey.
Ooh, I dig this tune.
Wait a minute.
["The Wizard and I" playing]
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
You know what we need?
May I kindly request
the presence
of the one and only
Cynthia Erivo?
[piano fanfare]
- Well, hello.
- Good.
Cynthia, well--
- Yes.
- Hey, would you be mad if we--
if we got to do something
a little bit together?
- I would love to do
something together.
- Geez.
I'm the luckiest guy on earth.
OK. Well--
- Yes?
- Listen to this.
Hey, Stephen Schwartz,
I've changed
some of the chords.
Listen up.
I hope you like it.
I hope it's OK.
- Oh, dear. OK.
- Just a little bit.
[soft piano music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Did that really
just happen? ♪
♪ Have I actually understood? ♪
♪ This weird quirk I've tried
to suppress or hide ♪
♪ Is a talent that could ♪
♪ Help me meet the Wizard ♪
[cheers and applause]
♪ If I make good ♪
♪ Mm ♪
♪ So I'll make ♪
♪ Good ♪
[music building]
♪ When I meet the Wizard ♪
♪ Once I prove my worth ♪
♪ Then I meet the Wizard ♪
♪ What I've waited for since ♪
♪ Well, since birth ♪
♪ And with all his
Wizard wisdom ♪
♪ By my looks,
he won't be blinded ♪
♪ Do you think
the Wizard is dumb ♪
♪ Or, like Munchkins,
so small-minded? ♪
♪ No ♪
♪ He'll say to me,
"I see who you truly are ♪
♪ A girl on whom I can rely" ♪
♪ And that's how we'll begin ♪
♪ Mm ♪
[jazzy piano music]
♪ The Wizard and I ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Once I'm with the Wizard ♪
♪ My whole life will change ♪
♪ 'Cause once you're
with the Wizard ♪
♪ No one thinks
you're strange ♪
♪ No father is
not proud of you ♪
♪ No sister acts ashamed ♪
♪ All of Oz has to love you ♪
♪ When by the Wizard
you're acclaimed ♪
♪ And this gift or this curse
I have inside ♪
♪ Maybe at last I'll know why ♪
♪ As we walk hand in hand ♪
♪ The Wizard and I ♪
♪ And one day he'll say to me,
"Elphaba ♪
♪ "A girl who is so superior ♪
♪ "Shouldn't a girl
who's so good inside ♪
♪ "Have a matching exterior? ♪
♪ "And since folks here,
to an absurd degree ♪
♪ "Seem fixated
on your verdigris ♪
♪ "Would it be
all right by you ♪
♪ If I degreenify you?" ♪
♪ And though, of course,
that's not important to me ♪
♪ "All right, why not?"
I'll reply ♪
♪ Oh, what a pair we'll be ♪
♪ The Wizard and I ♪
♪ Yes, what a pair we'll be ♪
♪ The Wizard and ♪
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
♪ Unlimited ♪
♪ My future is unlimited ♪
♪ And I've just had a vision
almost like a prophecy ♪
♪ I know
it sounds truly crazy ♪
♪ And true, the vision's hazy ♪
♪ But I swear
someday there'll be ♪
♪ A celebration throughout Oz ♪
♪ That's all to do ♪
♪ With me ♪
♪ And I'll stand there
with the Wizard ♪
♪ Feeling things
I've never felt ♪
♪ And though
I'd never show it ♪
♪ I'd be so happy
I could melt ♪
♪ And so it will be
for the rest of my life ♪
♪ And I'll want nothing else
till I die ♪
♪ Held in such high esteem ♪
♪ When people see me,
they will scream ♪
♪ For half of Oz's favorite ♪
♪ Team ♪
♪ The Wizard ♪
♪ And I ♪
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Hi, guys.
We have little seats.
- I like the palette.
- You look gorgeous.
That's a great color on you.
- I see.
Everybody, how's it feel
to be in the same room?
But before you answer that,
I just remembered
the very first experience
I had with the cast.
My dressing room was
next door to Ariana Grande.
And at that point...
- We were neighbors.
- I hadn't remembered
that we knew each other.
When Ariana was--
what was it, 11?
- Oh, yeah.
I went to see "The Pillowman."
- You went to see
"The Pillowman."
I was on Broadway
doing this show.
- And I waited by
the stage door to see you.
- Anyway, she came with her mom
and took a picture
of the two of us.
- At the stage door.
- But I saw her dressing room.
And Ariana was there.
- And you were wearing
a gold shirt and a top hat.
You looked so wizardly.
- Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
- You came in
in your Wizard duds.
- He looked fabulous.
It was amazing.
We were all like,
that's the Wizard.
- It must have been
very stressful
for, especially, Jon and Marc
to try and find
the most perfect cast
for this
because it's been around
for, what, 20-something years?
It's, like, if you
get it wrong, oh, my God.
Thunder and lightning
will strike you down.
- Yeah.
What were your audition
experiences like?
- Mine was sort of
the chemistry read.
So I go through the audition
and put everything out,
and I'm there for three hours.
And by the end of the audition,
I start running a 103 fever...
- Oh, gosh.
- And go home.
And I'm in bed
for, like, four days.
So at the time,
I have left the audition.
I'm like,
there's actually nothing left.
So I think whatever I had left
was in that room.
- I remember I'd sent a tape.
Crazy tape.
[laughter]
And I basically did
a karaoke version of it.
And--
- Which song did you do?
- I did--
I was gonna say "No Good Deed."
No, I did
"Dancing Through Life,"
but I did it at the five-minute
call when I was doing a play.
I'm worried about this section.
They're not gonna
suddenly cut to it.
♪ The trouble with schools is ♪
♪ They always try to teach
the wrong lessons ♪
♪ Believe me, I've been
kicked out of enough of them ♪
♪ To know ♪
- You have five minutes, team.
That's five minutes.
- I can't believe you did it
in your five-minute call.
How on Earth
did you even have--
- Well, because it was too--
you know,
it was the same thing.
It was such a bit--it's like
you sort of go, it's now.
I'd had the five-minute call
and said, just play it.
Let's just do it.
And I was getting ready.
And I just sang.
I sang it.
- Wow.
- Oh.
- But it was the only way I was
gonna be able to do that tape.
- Everyone just wanted
so earnestly
to serve this big,
beautiful piece
that is "Wicked," you know?
Everyone knows
that it's "Wicked."
No one and nothing is
bigger than this piece.
And everyone just showed up
as the most, like,
raw, authentic artist
they could be.
And everyone gave it their all.
It was really beautiful.
["One Short Day" playing]
- Please welcome Michelle Yeoh
and Marissa Bode.
[cheers and applause]
- Time for a special tribute
to all the fans
who took the song
"What Is This Feeling?"
and reimagined it
as an epic Super Bowl
halftime performance.
We all saw your TikToks,
and we loved
every single one of them.
[cheers and applause]
- And here to perform
"What Is This Feeling?"
like never before,
please welcome
Cynthia Erivo
and Ariana Grande.
[cheers and applause]
♪ both: Loathing ♪
♪ Unadulterated loathing ♪
- ♪ For your face ♪
- ♪ Your voice ♪
both: * Your clothing ♪
♪ Let's just say ♪
♪ I loathe it all ♪
["What Is This Feeling?"
playing]
♪ ♪
♪ Every little trait,
however small ♪
♪ Makes my very flesh
begin to crawl ♪
♪ With simple, utter loathing ♪
♪ There's a strange
exhilaration ♪
♪ In such total detestation ♪
♪ It's so pure, so strong ♪
♪ Though I do admit
it came on fast ♪
♪ Still, I do believe
that it can last ♪
♪ And I will be loathing,
loathing you ♪
♪ My whole life long ♪
- ♪ Dear Galinda,
you are just too good ♪
♪ How do you stand it?
I don't think I could ♪
♪ I don't think I could ♪
♪ ♪
[upbeat dance music]
- ♪ These things are sent
to try us ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ Poor Galinda,
forced to reside ♪
♪ With someone
so disgusticified ♪
♪ We just want to tell you ♪
♪ We're all on your side ♪
♪ We share your loathing ♪
both: * What is this feeling
so sudden and new ♪
- ♪ Unadulterated loathing ♪
both: * I felt the moment
I laid eyes on you ♪
- ♪ For her face, her voice,
her clothing ♪
both: * My pulse is rushing ♪
- ♪ Let's just say ♪
both: * My head is reeling ♪
- ♪ We loathe it all ♪
both:
♪ Oh, what is this feeling? ♪
- ♪ Every little trait,
however small ♪
both: * Does it have a name? ♪
♪ Yes ♪
♪ Ah ♪
[electronic music]
- ♪ O hallowed halls
and vine-draped walls ♪
♪ The proudliest sight
there is ♪
♪ When grey and sere
our hair hath turned ♪
♪ We shall still revere
the lessons learned ♪
♪ In our days
at dear old Shiz ♪
♪ Our days at dear old ♪
[trumpet playing]
[swing music]
♪ ♪
["What Is This Feeling?"]
♪ both: Loathing ♪
♪ There's a strange
exhilaration ♪
♪ In such total detestation ♪
♪ It's so pure, so strong ♪
♪ Though I do admit
it came on fast ♪
♪ Still, I do believe
that it can last ♪
♪ And I will be loathing
for forever ♪
♪ Loathing, truly, deeply ♪
♪ Loathing you ♪
♪ My whole life long ♪
- ♪ Loathing ♪
♪ Unadulterated loathing ♪
♪ ♪
- Boo!
- All right, I get it.
- [laughs]
[cheers and applause]
- "Wicked:
One Wonderful Night"
is brought to you by Lexus.
["One Short Day" playing]
♪ ♪
- "Wicked" resonated with fans
all around the world
and invited them
not only to watch
but to engage with our world.
In fact, a lot of moments
from the movie
took on a life of their own,
whether it be
Ariana's hair flip...
- Toss, toss.
- The "Defying Gravity" riff
that so many have tried
to recreate...
- [vocalizing]
[cheers and applause]
[laughter]
- Very nice.
Some of you even
painted yourself green.
- It won't wash off.
It's been a year!
- Yeah, you've got to use
a special soap for your face.
- What about
the rest of my body?
- Well, how much of your body
have you covered in green?
- Everything.
- Everything?
- Oh, dear.
Well, we'll just have to get
you a doctor for that, OK?
Meanwhile, let's take a look
at just how much of an impact
this film has had
across the world.
both: "Wicked"!
- ♪ Dear Galinda,
you are just too good ♪
- I love "Wicked"!
- ♪ How do you stand it?
I don't think I could ♪
- We love "Wicked" so much.
- "Wicked"!
- We're "Wicked" superfans.
- I've been watching "Wicked"
every day.
both: * Loathing for forever ♪
- Loving "Wicked"
isn't a hobby for me.
It is a lifestyle.
both: * Loathing you ♪
- I am just
absolutely obsessed.
It is everything.
both: * My whole life long ♪
- My favorite character
is Elphaba
because she can fly
just like me.
- ♪ Dancing through life ♪
♪ Down at the Ozdust ♪
- ♪ If only because dust
is what we come to ♪
- ♪ Nothing matters,
but knowing nothing matters ♪
♪ It's just life ♪
both: Come on.
Hop into the "Wicked" world.
- ♪ It's just life ♪
- [gasps]
- ♪ So if you care
to find me ♪
- "Wicked" has had
a huge impact on my life.
- ♪ As someone
told me lately ♪
♪ Everyone deserves
a chance to fly ♪
- "Wicked" has
this timeless power.
- It motivated me to keep
fighting for my dreams.
- I just feel like I could
take on the world.
- It was the best thing
I've ever seen.
I sat there sobbing.
- It became something
that I could wrap myself up in
to get through
the rough times.
- If Elphaba can do it with
the whole world against her,
then I can do it too.
- Yeah, it makes me feel happy.
Happy, happy, happy.
- Thank you for everything.
Mwah.
- [vocalizing]
- Good job!
- Now cut.
[cheers and applause]
- Oh, my goodness.
I wonder what song
is coming next.
The love that we have
received from our fans
all over the world has been
truly so amazing and so moving.
And one of those fans
that you've just seen
in that incredible montage
happens to be
in our audience tonight.
So I wanted to know...
Remington.
Hello.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Is this OK?
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Yeah.
- I loved your video.
- Thanks.
[laughter]
- How old are you?
- Four.
- Oh, my goodness.
Well, I love your outfit.
- Thanks.
[laughter]
- Well, I was wondering,
since you're dressed
like Elphie,
would you be my Elphie
for this next song, please?
- Yeah.
- Thank you so much.
Oh, my goodness,
I'm so excited.
Come this way.
Thank you.
Hi.
[cheers and applause]
Oh, my goodness.
It's nice to meet you.
Come here.
Do you mind if I--
do you want me
to take this for you?
It's not going anywhere.
Don't worry.
Now, can you get up here?
Is that OK?
[laughter and applause]
- Are you comfy there?
Is that OK?
You know the scene.
Hi, Remy.
Is it OK if I call you Remy?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
- OK. Thank you.
I was gonna
call you that anyway
because, Remy,
now that we're friends...
[giggles]
[cheers and applause]
Now that we're friends,
I've decided to make you
my new project.
- Yeah.
[laughter]
Yeah.
I know.
That's what makes me so nice.
[bell dings]
♪ Whenever I see someone
less fortunate than I ♪
♪ And let's face it, right,
who isn't ♪
♪ Less fortunate than I? ♪
♪ My tender heart tends
to start to bleed ♪
♪ And when someone needs
a makeover ♪
♪ I simply have to take over ♪
♪ I know this, I know ♪
OK?
♪ Exactly what they need ♪
♪ And even in your case ♪
♪ Though it's the toughest case
I've yet to face ♪
♪ Don't worry ♪
♪ I'm determined to succeed ♪
♪ Follow my lead ♪
♪ And yes, indeed ♪
♪ You will be ♪
♪ Popular ♪
♪ You're gonna be popular ♪
♪ I'll teach you
the proper ploys ♪
♪ When you talk to boys ♪
♪ Little ways to flirt
and flounce, ooh! ♪
♪ I'll show you
what shoes to wear ♪
♪ How to fix your hair ♪
♪ Everything
that really counts ♪
♪ To be popular ♪
♪ I'll help you be popular ♪
♪ You'll hang
with the right cohorts ♪
♪ You'll be good at sports ♪
♪ Know the slang
you've got to know ♪
♪ So let's start ♪
♪ 'Cause you've got
an awfully long ♪
♪ Way to go ♪
Come with me.
Come on.
Down center stage.
♪ Don't be offended
by my frank analysis ♪
♪ Think of it
as personality dialysis ♪
♪ Now that I've chosen
to become a pal ♪
♪ A sister and advisor ♪
♪ There's nobody wiser ♪
♪ Not when it comes
to popular ♪
♪ I know about popular ♪
♪ And with an assist from me
to be who you'll be ♪
♪ Instead of dreary
who you were ♪
♪ Well, are ♪
♪ There's nothing
that can stop you ♪
♪ From becoming popular ♪
♪ Lar ♪
♪ La, la ♪
♪ We're gonna make you
popular ♪
[squeals]
♪ When I see
depressing creatures ♪
♪ With unprepossessing
features ♪
♪ I remind them
on their own behalf ♪
♪ To think of ♪
♪ Celebrated heads of state ♪
♪ Or especially great
communicators ♪
♪ Did they have
brains or knowledge? ♪
♪ Don't make me laugh ♪
♪ They were ♪
- Popular.
- Exactly.
That's what I'm saying.
♪ It's not about aptitude ♪
♪ It's the way you're viewed ♪
♪ So it's very shrewd to be ♪
♪ Very, very popular like me ♪
[laughs]
[bright music]
Now, Remy, would you mind
coming with me?
I'd like to teach you
how to toss your hair.
Ready?
Now, this is
a slightly different technique
because I have a ponytail
today.
But I have to wind it up.
And then you toss, toss.
[gasps]
[cheers and applause]
No notes, Rem.
It's been a pleasure.
I have one more thing
before you go,
a parting gift.
This is my training wand.
I hope you enjoy it.
Thank you, Remy.
Can I have a hug?
[cheers and applause]
You're amazing.
Thank you so much.
Everyone, Remington.
[cheers and applause]
Well, hello.
[bell dings]
♪ And though you protest ♪
♪ Your disinterest ♪
♪ I know clandestinely ♪
♪ You're gonna
grin and bear it ♪
♪ Your newfound popularity ♪
[squeals]
♪ La, la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ You'll be popular ♪
♪ Just not quite as popular ♪
♪ As me ♪
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
- After the break,
a breathtaking performance
from the Gershwin Theatre
when Ariana and Cynthia
join Stephen Schwartz
and two very special guests.
["One Short Day" playing]
- Please welcome Ethan Slater
and Bowen Yang.
♪ ♪
- Hello.
- Grab me now.
- We're here, Bowen.
You got this.
- Please excuse our appearance.
- Sorry.
- We were watching Ariana
and Remy perform "Popular"
backstage and got
a little overexcited
during the hair toss.
- Yeah.
So to all the kids
watching at home,
remember to stretch
before you toss.
Now, back to what
really matters.
We go now to the iconic
Gershwin Theatre
in New York City,
the original home
of the Broadway production
"Wicked."
Accompanied by the
incomparable Stephen Schwartz,
with a special arrangement
and performance
just for tonight,
this is "For Good."
[soft piano music]
♪ ♪
- Hey, guys.
- Hi.
- We're at the Gershwin.
- I know.
- Who thought
that would happen?
- I don't know.
- You guys look beautiful.
You should probably
sing something.
What do you think?
- I think it's a good idea.
- All right.
Let's do it.
- Why not?
- How about this?
["For Good" playing]
♪ ♪
- ♪ I've heard it said ♪
♪ That people come
into our lives ♪
♪ For a reason ♪
♪ Bringing something
we must learn ♪
♪ And we are led ♪
♪ To those
who help us most to grow ♪
♪ If we let them ♪
♪ And we help them in return ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Well, I don't know
if I believe that's true ♪
♪ But I know
I'm who I am today ♪
♪ Because I knew you ♪
♪ Like a comet
pulled from orbit ♪
♪ As it passes a sun ♪
♪ Like a stream
that meets a boulder ♪
♪ Halfway through the wood ♪
♪ Who can say if I've been
changed for the better? ♪
♪ But because I knew you ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I have been changed ♪
♪ For good ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ It well may be ♪
♪ That we will
never meet again ♪
♪ In this lifetime ♪
♪ So let me say
before we part ♪
♪ So much of me is made ♪
♪ Of what I learned from you ♪
♪ You'll be with me ♪
♪ Like a handprint
on my heart ♪
♪ And now
whatever way our stories end ♪
♪ I know
you have rewritten mine ♪
♪ By being my friend ♪
♪ Like a ship blown
from its mooring ♪
♪ By a wind off the sea ♪
♪ Like a seed dropped
by a skybird ♪
♪ In a distant wood ♪
♪ Who can say if I've been
changed for the better ♪
♪ But because I knew you ♪
- ♪ Because I knew you ♪
both: * I have been
changed for good ♪
- ♪ The years go by so fast ♪
♪ The flames keep burning ♪
♪ But we know someday
it could be gone ♪
- ♪ It's nice to know then ♪
♪ As the torch gets passed ♪
both: * You will keep it
blazing brightly on ♪
both: * Like a comet
pulled from orbit ♪
both: * Like a ship blown
from its mooring ♪
both: * As it passes the sun ♪
both: * By a wind off the sea ♪
both: * Like a stream
that meets a boulder ♪
both: * Like a seed dropped
by a bird in the wood ♪
both:
♪ Halfway through the wood ♪
both: * Who can say ♪
♪ If I've been changed
for the better ♪
both: * I do believe
I have been ♪
♪ Changed for the better ♪
- ♪ And because I knew you ♪
- ♪ Because I knew you ♪
all: * Because I knew you ♪
♪ I have been changed ♪
♪ ♪
♪ For good ♪
- There's such a capacity
for the fans
to love the films
alongside the musical,
alongside the books,
alongside
the L. Frank Baum books.
Like, it is more likely
than not
that fans are
a little bit adversarial
towards the newer thing,
the newer installment,
the newer imagination
of something.
I think the fact
that none of us
have really encountered any
sort of like, I don't know--
- Pushback.
- Pushback is so meaningful.
- We're very lucky to have been
embraced by the fans
the way we have.
The "Wicked" fans are the most
beautiful souls in the world.
And they're fiercely loving.
- Yeah.
- Oh, my gosh.
- They're so insanely loving.
It's crazy.
- The love and passion
that you've poured
into each character
has really allowed them
and opened their hearts
and minds to us.
- We all love our characters.
I remember you defending
the Wizard to the end.
And, you know, I don't know
if that's how you feel
now that we're out of it,
but you have to, like, love--
you have to love
your character.
And so I love Boq so much.
- I was there too. Yeah.
- Yeah.
- I take away a lot
from you guys.
But what helps me is, like,
when I look into your eyes,
and I see Elphaba, and I see
all the complexities there.
Then you find that exchange.
And I love when I look at you,
you're, like, fresh and naive.
And then Jon will
come up to me and say,
scare the hell out of Ariana.
And I'm like, are you sure?
He says, yes.
So I just turned and ran
at her, literally like--
[shouting]
This poor--
- Best moment of my life.
- She dropped onto the couch.
- [gasps]
- Wave.
And shut your mouth!
- She was so scared,
a contact lens popped out.
[laughs]
- [laughing]
My contact came out.
I'm sorry, y'all.
- It was
a really cherished moment.
- I loved scaring you.
[laughter]
- I savor every minute.
- And now you--let's get
to this half of the room,
because I want to hear
about this.
- Bowen, what about Pfannee?
- Bowen. The besties.
- I've learned, like,
the danger of cruelty from him.
These are two people
who are, like, bullies.
And they--and they--
and they execute and motivate
other people to do bad things.
But I would apologize
to Cynthia between takes
and be like, that felt awful,
like, being cruel to you.
So I think--I don't know,
I think as you age,
you just soften a little bit
in those ways, hopefully.
And I feel like
that is the thing
that I've taken away from him.
- Yes. Yeah. Yeah.
- We're so privileged
to have been able to be there,
to witness each other's moments
and see every single take
of everything
because the movie
is so beautiful.
And everyone is
so brilliant in it.
But it was so special
to be there
and see everyone's process
and every single ad lib
and every single choice
that everyone made.
And it was just such a treat.
- Well done, everyone.
- Yeah.
- Please welcome Bowen Yang
and Ariana Grande.
["One Short Day" playing]
- You know,
when you think about it,
"Wicked" is a film at its core
about friendship.
- I couldn't agree more.
- Yes.
Friendship between two people
who couldn't be more different
from each other.
- Yes, a popular,
ambitious sorcery student
with impeccable style
and a love for all things pink.
- And her best friend Pfannee.
[laughter]
- Oh.
- What?
- No, nothing.
I just thought you were--
I thought you were going
to say, you know, Elphaba.
- Elphaba?
Really?
- Well, yeah.
- Oh, well--
- That's, like, the core
friendship of the whole movie.
- I don't know.
I feel like "Wicked" is a story
about a popular girl
and an equally popular guy
who loves to follow her around,
carry her books,
and occasionally makes
catty little comments
about their ugly classmates.
- I really don't think
that's what
people are taking away from--
but yeah.
- Well, art is subjective.
- Yeah, it is.
That's true.
I love you.
- I love you.
- So much.
- In the meantime,
performing "I'm Not That Girl,"
please welcome the phenomenal,
the singular Cynthia Erivo.
[cheers and applause]
["I'm Not That Girl" playing]
[yearning music]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Hands touch ♪
♪ Eyes meet ♪
♪ Sudden silence ♪
♪ Sudden heat ♪
♪ Hearts leap ♪
♪ In a giddy whirl ♪
♪ He could be that boy ♪
♪ But I'm not that girl ♪
♪ Don't dream ♪
♪ Too far ♪
♪ Don't lose sight
of who you are ♪
♪ Don't remember
that rush of joy ♪
♪ He could be that boy ♪
♪ I'm not that girl ♪
♪ Every so often,
we long to steal ♪
♪ To the land
of what-might-have-been ♪
♪ But that doesn't soften
the ache we feel ♪
♪ When reality sets back in ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Blithe smile ♪
♪ Lithe limb ♪
♪ She who's winsome ♪
♪ She wins him ♪
♪ Gold hair ♪
♪ With a gentle curl ♪
♪ That's the girl he chose ♪
♪ And heaven knows ♪
♪ I'm not that girl ♪
[vocalizing]
♪ ♪
♪ Don't wish ♪
♪ Don't start ♪
♪ Wishing only wounds
the heart ♪
♪ I wasn't born ♪
♪ For the rose and pearl ♪
♪ ♪
♪ There's a girl I know ♪
♪ He loves her so ♪
♪ Mm ♪
♪ I'm not that girl ♪
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
Thank you.
[laughs]
♪ ♪
["One Short Day" playing]
- And now, please welcome
the director of "Wicked"
and "Wicked: For Good"
Jon M. Chu.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
- Wow.
I am Jon M. Chu.
I am the director of "Wicked."
Four-plus years of my life
poured into this.
My wife had three kids
during this.
Superstar.
Anyway,
directing this movie has been
one of the highlights
of my career,
but I knew
from the very beginning,
I had to get the casting
just right.
And we ended up
with the perfect cast.
Right?
[cheers and applause]
But I have to tell you all
that so many different people
wanted to be in "Wicked"
and sent us
their casting tapes.
You may have heard this.
And tonight,
for the first time,
we are sharing
some of the unseen footage
from the "Wicked" auditions.
Take a look.
["Defying Gravity" playing]
- My name is
Chris "Ludacris" Bridges,
and I'll be reading for Glinda
because I want to show people
that I have range.
- Lainey Wilson
reading for Elphaba.
- My name is Ben Schwartz.
- I'm Rob Gronkowski,
a.k.a. The Gronk.
- Do me a favor.
Don't stand there. Thank you.
- Hi, I'm Shaquille O'Neal,
and I'm reading for the part
of Munchkin Number Five.
- Seven.
- Oh, Munchkin Number Seven.
- I'm Khloe Kardashian,
and I'm auditioning for Glinda
because she's a good bitch.
I mean, witch. Witch.
- ♪ So if you care to find me ♪
- ♪ Look to the western sky ♪
- ♪ Ew, I'll show you
what shoes to wear ♪
- I am auditioning
for the part of Glinda.
Toss, toss.
Hello.
- ♪ The toughest case
I've yet to face ♪
♪ Don't worry ♪
♪ I'm determined ♪
- ♪ You could be that boy ♪
♪ And I could be that girl ♪
- Five, six, seven, eight.
♪ And if I'm flying solo ♪
♪ At least I'm-- ♪
What's that?
She's already been cast?
Not a problem.
I didn't know
which character, so--
♪ Popular ♪
- ♪ You're gonna be popular ♪
- ♪ Popular ♪
- Popular.
You gon' be popular.
- ♪ I'll teach you
the proper ploys ♪
♪ When you talk to boys ♪
- ♪ You're gonna be pop-- ♪
What's that?
She's cast as well?
So who do you want me
to audition--
flying monkey.
Sure.
Yeah, you got it.
♪ I'm just a fly-- ♪
He doesn't sing?
Or talk? OK.
- ♪ I wanna be on the broom
where it happens ♪
♪ The broom where it happens ♪
- "Defying Gravity"
battle cry.
- Here's my big finish,
Jon Chu.
[vocalizing]
- [vocalizing]
- [pitchy vocalization]
- [screaming]
Now that's wicked.
[cheers and applause]
- Please welcome Bowen Yang.
- Hello, everyone.
Oh, aren't you nice?
Hi, everyone.
I know we're all
having fun tonight,
but this is actually
a huge night for me.
I don't know if you know this,
but I originally
went out for Fiyero.
I didn't get the part
because Jon M. Chu said
that I was
"too conventionally attractive"
and that "rejection would
make me a better Pfannee."
That's the name
of my character.
Did you know that?
Most people don't.
But he was nice enough
to let me be
Fiyero's understudy,
which many have told me
is not a job in movies.
But seeing as Jonathan Bailey
couldn't be here tonight...
[cheers and applause]
I am proud to be
your Fiyero this evening.
And all I have to say is...
♪ The trouble with schools is ♪
♪ They always try to teach
the wrong lesson ♪
["Dancing Through Life"
playing]
♪ Believe me, I've been
kicked out of enough of them ♪
♪ To know ♪
♪ They want you to become
less callow ♪
♪ Less shallow ♪
Guys.
♪ But I say,
why invite stress in? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Stop studying strife ♪
♪ And learn to live ♪
♪ The unexamined ♪
♪ Life ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Dancing through life ♪
♪ Skimming the surface ♪
♪ Gliding where turf
is smooth ♪
♪ Life's more painless ♪
[grunts]
♪ For the brainless ♪
♪ Why think too hard
when it's so soothing ♪
♪ Dancing through life? ♪
♪ No need to tough it ♪
♪ When you can
slough it off as I do ♪
♪ Nothing matters,
but knowing nothing matters ♪
♪ It's just life ♪
♪ So keep dancing through ♪
- Hey, Bowen.
- Ethan, what the Boq
are you doing?
- Nice job working my character
name into the segment.
But tonight,
I'm Fiyero's understudy.
- No, I'm Fiyero's understudy.
- According to who?
- According to Chu, Jon M. Chu.
Hey, what does the M stand for?
- I think movies.
- Yeah, movies.
Get those Fiyero duds
off of you right now.
- Wait.
Hold on, Bowen.
I think I hear
our cue coming up.
both: * Dancing through life ♪
♪ Swaying and sweeping ♪
- ♪ And always keeping cool ♪
- ♪ Life is fraughtless
when you're thoughtless ♪
- ♪ Those who don't try
never look foolish ♪
♪ Dancing through life ♪
♪ Mindless and careless ♪
♪ Make sure you're where
less trouble is rife ♪
♪ Woes are fleeting ♪
♪ Blows are glancing ♪
♪ When you're dancing ♪
♪ Through life ♪
Whoo!
♪ ♪
- Thank you.
- That was cool.
That was really good.
Let's go. Come on.
♪ ♪
Whoa, Marissa.
What in the Nessa
are you doing here?
- I'm the Fiyero understudy.
- No, you are not!
- What are you saying,
a woman can't play Fiyero?
- No, I think all women
should play all roles.
You know this about me.
- So what's the big problem?
- Well, we can't all be Fiyero.
It's a little bit confusing.
- It's really not.
Tonight's our night.
And there's no rule that says
we can't all be Fiyero.
- Maybe Marissa's right.
- Yeah, maybe Marissa's right.
Because Fiyero
isn't just a person.
He's a feeling.
- The feeling
of wanting attention.
We can all relate to that.
Let's do as all Fiyeros do.
all: * Let's go down
to the Ozdust Ballroom ♪
♪ We'll meet there
later tonight ♪
♪ ♪
♪ We can dance
till it's light ♪
♪ Find the prettiest girl ♪
♪ Give her a whirl ♪
♪ Right on down
to the Ozdust Ballroom ♪
♪ Come on, follow me ♪
♪ You'll be happy to be there ♪
♪ Dancing through life ♪
- ♪ Down at the Ozdust ♪
all: * If only because dust
is what we come to ♪
♪ Nothing matters,
but knowing nothing matters ♪
♪ It's just life ♪
♪ So keep dancing through ♪
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
- You're good.
- No, no. Oh.
You're good.
- You're good.
all: We're good.
- ♪ Dancing through life ♪
♪ Down at the Ozdust ♪
♪ If only because dust ♪
♪ Is what we come to ♪
- Yes!
- ♪ While you're dancing ♪
♪ Through ♪
[cheers and applause]
[sweeping music]
- Please give a warm welcome
to Academy Award winner
Michelle Yeoh.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
- Oh, my God.
Yes.
You are truly wicked.
OK?
Next up, we've got
an amazing performance
of one of the most
beloved songs
from the "Wicked" universe.
Performing
a special arrangement
of "Thank Goodness,"
for just tonight,
please welcome the enchanting,
the incomparable Ariana Grande.
[cheers and applause]
- I love you, Michelle.
["Thank Goodness" playing]
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- Let's go, Ari!
- [giggles]
♪ We couldn't be happier ♪
♪ Right, dear? ♪
♪ Couldn't be happier
right here ♪
♪ Look what we've got ♪
♪ A fairytale plot ♪
♪ Our very own happy ending ♪
♪ Where we couldn't
be happier ♪
♪ True, dear? ♪
♪ Couldn't be happier ♪
♪ And we're happy to share
our ending vicariously ♪
♪ With all of you ♪
♪ He couldn't look handsomer ♪
♪ I couldn't feel humbler ♪
♪ We couldn't be happier ♪
♪ Because happy is
what happens ♪
♪ When all your dreams
come true ♪
♪ ♪
♪ That's why ♪
♪ I couldn't be happier ♪
♪ No, I couldn't be happier ♪
♪ Though it is, I admit,
the tiniest bit ♪
♪ Unlike I anticipated ♪
♪ But I couldn't be happier ♪
♪ Simply couldn't be happier ♪
♪ Well, not "simply" ♪
♪ 'Cause getting your dreams ♪
♪ It's strange, but it seems ♪
♪ A little, well, complicated ♪
♪ There's a kind of
a sort of cost ♪
♪ There's a couple of things
get lost ♪
♪ There are bridges you cross ♪
♪ You didn't know you crossed ♪
♪ Until you crossed ♪
♪ And if that joy,
that thrill ♪
♪ Doesn't thrill ♪
♪ Like you think it will ♪
♪ Still,
with this perfect finale ♪
♪ The cheers and the ballyhoo ♪
♪ Who wouldn't be happier? ♪
♪ So I couldn't be happier ♪
♪ Because happy
is what happens ♪
♪ When all your dreams
come true ♪
♪ Well, isn't it? ♪
♪ Happy is what happens ♪
♪ When your dreams ♪
♪ Come ♪
♪ True ♪
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
- OK. Shh.
She's concentrating.
- Oh, God,
this is very serious.
- What are you guys up to?
- Michelle's taking
one of those
"Which 'Wicked' Character
Are You?" quizzes.
- Oh, fun.
- OK, done.
And the "Wicked" character
I'm most like is--
[laughs] Madame Morrible.
- Right on the money.
- Nailed it.
- Wait, that's who you play
in the movie.
- Great.
Madame Morrible.
- That's crazy.
- Exactly, bingo.
Let me try. Yeah.
Good, good, good, good.
OK. Let's see.
[vocalizing]
Very good.
I like quizzes.
OK. And done.
The character
you're most like in "Wicked."
I'll be a ring-tailed monkey.
It's the Wizard.
- Wow.
- Oh, wow. What a surprise.
- And that's your character.
- Yes.
- This is incredible.
- Incredible.
- I have to try.
- Yeah, you must try.
- Try it.
- Yes. Yes.
Oh, yeah.
I think I know
who he's gonna be.
- OK.
- They list
every character's name...
- OK, and the "Wicked"
character I am most like is--
- OK.
- Elphaba's broom?
- Interesting.
- Oh, golly.
- Elphaba's broom
is not a character.
Why is this even an option?
- I can kind of see it.
- Yeah, I totally see it.
- His posture is straight.
- I don't know
what about me is giving
Elphaba's broom
besides the fact
that I wipe the floor
with y'all.
- Ooh. Ooh.
That's harsh.
- Hey, Bowen, do you mind
helping me open this?
It's a little--what are you--
what are you guys up to?
- We're taking one of those
"Which 'Wicked' Character
Are You?" quizzes.
Bowen got Elphaba's broom.
- That's ridiculous.
- Thank you.
My man Ethan.
- I cannot believe
I haven't seen it before.
You are--
you are so Elphaba's broom.
- Right?
- Look at his face now.
I think it's bristling.
You get it?
Bristles. Broom.
- Guys, are we really gonna let
some silly little quiz
tell us who we are?
That's not what
"Wicked" is about.
"Wicked" is about
having the courage
to be who you are no matter
what the world tells you.
And with that,
I bid you farewell.
- [gasps]
That's exactly how I imagined
Elphaba's broom would
sweep away.
- Not cool, Legend.
- Mwah.
I love you still.
[door slams]
- Please put
your hands together
for Cynthia Erivo
and Ariana Grande.
[cheers and applause]
- We have
a very special surprise
for everyone
in the audience tonight.
- Yes, if you would just look
under your seats--
- No, no, Ariana,
we cut that bit.
- Oh.
Just kidding.
- What we're excited about
is that "Wicked: For Good"
will feature
two brand-new songs
written exclusively
for the movie.
- And tonight we are
thrilled to share
a sneak peek of them both.
[cheers and applause]
The first song is sung
stunningly by Cynthia.
And it's about Elphaba's
dedication to protecting Oz,
even as she faces rejection
from everyone around her.
It's called
"No Place Like Home."
- The second original song
is a poignant solo
sung wonderfully by Ariana,
called "The Girl
in the Bubble."
It captures the moment
where Glinda decides
not to just call herself good,
but to truly become
Glinda the Good.
Let's take a special look
at both.
[soft dramatic music]
- ♪ Why do I love this place ♪
♪ That's never loved me? ♪
♪ There's no place like home ♪
♪ There's no place ♪
♪ Like ♪
♪ Home ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ There's that ♪
♪ Beautiful girl ♪
♪ With a beautiful life ♪
♪ Such a beautiful life
built on lies ♪
♪ For the girl in the bubble ♪
♪ The pink shiny bubble ♪
♪ Isn't it high time ♪
♪ For her bubble
♪ To pop? ♪
- All of the music performed
in tonight's broadcast special
is available now.
- Please welcome Marissa Bode.
[cheers and applause]
["Dancing Through Life"
playing]
♪ ♪
- "Wicked" is filled
with so many incredible songs,
but there is one
that stands out.
It's connected
with so many people
from all over the world.
I'm talking, of course,
about "Defying Gravity."
[cheers and applause]
The song is an ode
to authenticity
and about believing in yourself
no matter what obstacles
the world puts in your way.
Performing "Defying Gravity,"
please welcome
the incredible Cynthia Erivo.
[cheers and applause]
["Defying Gravity" playing]
♪ ♪
- ♪ Something has
changed within me ♪
♪ Something is not the same ♪
♪ I'm through with playing by ♪
♪ The rules
of someone else's game ♪
♪ Too late
for second-guessing ♪
to go back to sleep ♪
♪ It's time
to trust my instincts ♪
♪ Close my eyes ♪
♪ And leap ♪
♪ It's time to try
defying gravity ♪
♪ I think I'll try
♪ And you can't pull me down ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I'm through
accepting limits ♪
♪ 'Cause someone says
they're so ♪
♪ Some things I cannot change ♪
♪ But till I try,
I'll never know ♪
♪ Too long I've been afraid
of losing love ♪
♪ I guess I've lost ♪
♪ Well, if that's love ♪
♪ It comes at much too high
a cost ♪
♪ I'd sooner buy
defying gravity ♪
♪ Kiss me goodbye ♪
♪ I'm defying gravity ♪
♪ And you can't pull me down ♪
♪ ♪
♪ It's me ♪
♪ So if you care to find me ♪
♪ Look to the western sky ♪
♪ As someone told me lately ♪
♪ Everyone deserves
a chance to fly ♪
♪ And if I'm flying solo ♪
♪ At least I'm flying free ♪
♪ To those who'd ground me ♪
♪ Take a message back from me ♪
♪ Tell them
how I am defying gravity ♪
♪ I'm flying high,
defying gravity ♪
♪ And soon I'll match them
in renown ♪
♪ And nobody in all of Oz ♪
♪ No Wizard
that there is or was ♪
♪ Is ever gonna bring ♪
♪ Me down ♪
- ♪ Look at her, she's wicked,
kill her! ♪
- ♪ Bring me down ♪
- ♪ So we've got to bring her ♪
- [vocalizing]
- ♪ Down ♪
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
- OK.
This involves pointing.
- Pointing.
- So this is a game
of Most Likely To.
Everyone point
to the person you think
is most likely to, first,
steal a costume from wardrobe.
I don't want to cast
aspersions on--
- Yes, you can. No.
- Are they pointing to you?
- No, we're not
pointing to you.
- I'm completely shielded.
- We're pointing to--
- This lady here.
- Me?
- Yeah.
We're pointing to--
- Well, I've owned this.
I have addressed this.
I have stolen.
[laughter]
- I'm a thief.
- I have stolen
from the closet of Glinda.
- I think we all may have
taken a thing or two.
- Yes.
- A memorabilia.
Yes.
- OK. Next.
Most likely to burst into song.
- Oh, yeah, actually.
Yeah. For sure.
- Yeah. I apologize.
- Absolutely.
- Whenever he's nervous,
he sings.
- Always songs with good--
with good in the title.
- OK, most likely to end up
a director.
- Ooh.
- Why are you pointing--
- I would love--
- Because you want
to be a director.
- All of you.
I'd say all of you.
- And Ethan definitely.
- Directing definitely.
- I feel like
the fingers can go--
- Everyone is so creative
and brilliant here.
- I don't know if it's likely,
but I'd like to.
- This is too damn hard.
- Most likely to accidentally
spoil the plot in an interview.
[laughter]
Yeah.
- Bowen's like,
there's this one thing
that they cut that they said
never to mention
or show anyone ever.
That was awesome.
It was this.
That's you, but it's amazing.
- What a wonderful, like,
ragtag bunch of folks we are
to get to be able
to do this together.
Meant to be, for sure,
because I can't really imagine
doing this
with anyone else, you know?
- We won't see
each other sometimes
maybe months, maybe years.
But I think
when we do see each other,
we will just pick up
where we left off.
- That's right.
- Yeah.
- We should do this again.
We should do it more often.
- I would be down for this.
- We'll take some.
We'll put them in boxes.
- Someone take
the flowers home.
- Oh.
- Don't wanna waste 'em.
- I love flowers.
- That's too cute.
Look at you.
- Yeah. Good.
Why don't we help you?
I'll help you.
You got it?
Oh, God.
- And we are stealing.
- You got it? OK.
- We are stealing from the set.
- Is this bolted down?
- It's a really nice table.
- I'll take the pastries.
- Oh, no,
don't steal the table.
- Oh, yeah,
that might be too much.
- Oh, my God.
- OK. Bye, guys.
See you later.
- Off you go.
- Yeah. Good point.
Thank you so much.
All right.
- So much left.
All right. Well, here we are.
[cheers and applause]
- "Wicked" is a movie
that teaches us
to look beneath the surface
and see the beauty
in our differences.
- And Oz has always been
a magical place
that celebrates uniqueness
and embraces
every color of the rainbow.
- In times like these
that feel so divided,
as if we're reading
from different pages
and different books...
- We want you all to know
that you're never alone.
And you're safe with us.
And we love you so much.
[cheers and applause]
["Get Happy/Happy Days
Are Here Again" playing]
♪ Forget your troubles ♪
- ♪ Happy days ♪
- ♪ Come on, get happy ♪
- ♪ Are here again ♪
- ♪ You better chase ♪
- ♪ The skies above ♪
- ♪ Your cares away ♪
- ♪ Are clear again ♪
- ♪ Shout hallelujah ♪
- ♪ So let's sing a song ♪
- ♪ Come on, get happy ♪
- ♪ Of cheer again ♪
- ♪ Get ready ♪
- ♪ Happy days ♪
- ♪ For the Judgment Day ♪
- ♪ Are here again ♪
- ♪ The sun is shining ♪
- ♪ All together ♪
- ♪ Come on, get happy ♪
- ♪ Shout it now ♪
- ♪ The Lord is waiting ♪
- ♪ There's no one ♪
- ♪ To take your hand ♪
- ♪ Who can doubt it now ♪
- ♪ Shout hallelujah ♪
- ♪ So let's tell the world ♪
- ♪ And just get happy ♪
- ♪ About it now ♪
- ♪ We're going ♪
- ♪ Happy days ♪
- ♪ To the promised land ♪
- ♪ Are here again ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ We're heading
'cross the river ♪
♪ Soon your cares
will all be gone ♪
- ♪ There'll be no more ♪
♪ From now on ♪
both: * From now on ♪
- ♪ Forget your troubles ♪
- ♪ Happy days ♪
- ♪ Come on, get happy ♪
- ♪ Are here again ♪
- ♪ You better chase ♪
- ♪ The skies above ♪
- ♪ Your blues away ♪
- ♪ Are clear again ♪
- ♪ Shout hallelujah ♪
- ♪ So let's sing a song ♪
- ♪ And just get happy ♪
- ♪ Of cheer again ♪
- ♪ Happy times ♪
- ♪ Happy nights ♪
both: * Happy days are here ♪
♪ Again ♪
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]